in this screencast we'll have a look at
在这个截屏视频中，我们将看一下
the community support in IntelliJ IDEA
IntelliJ IDEA中的社区支持
and the other IDs from JetBrains in
以及JetBrains中的其他ID
addition to syntax highlighting for the
除了语法高亮显示
configuration files with kubernetes
Kubernetes的配置文件
support we get code completion
支持我们获得代码完成
inspections and navigation we can use
可以使用的检查和导航
the gutter icons for navigation between
排水沟图标之间的导航
the definition and usages of the labels
标签的定义和用法
and we can rename the label safely by
我们可以通过以下方式安全地重命名标签
using shift of 6 shortcut it is also
使用6快捷键的移位它也是
possible to navigate by pressing command
可以通过按命令进行导航
B or control B it is possible to define
B或控件B可以定义
multiple resources within the same file
同一文件中有多个资源
let's try adding a new resource by
让我们尝试通过添加新资源
pressing command J or control J shortcut
按下命令J或控制J快捷键
we get a list of life templates that are
我们得到了生活模板的列表
available in this context there are a
在这种情况下可用
few predefined templates for config map
一些预定义的配置映射模板
deployment service and pod
部署服务和Pod
configurations just as an example let's
配置作为一个例子，让我们
use the generic resource template to
使用通用资源模板来
create the deployment configuration as
创建部署配置为
you can see code completion works not
你可以看到代码完成工作不
only for the configuration parameters
仅用于配置参数
but also for the values it is now
而且对于现在的价值
advanced that some of the configuration
高级一些配置
parameters require multiple arguments so
参数需要多个参数，因此
the completion automatically creates the
完成自动创建
nested elements and guides you in the
嵌套元素并指导您
authoring process the quick
创作过程快速
documentation pop-up is useful for
文档弹出窗口对于
checking the information about the
检查有关的信息
specific elements in this example for
此示例中的特定元素
the image pool Policy parameter we can
图像池Policy参数，我们可以
see that this parameter is an
看到这个参数是一个
enumeration hence all the possible
因此，所有可能的枚举
values are known upfront so we can use
值是预先已知的，因此我们可以使用
basic completion by pressing control
按下控制即可完成基本操作
space and select the desired value from
空格并从中选择所需的值
the list the file
列出文件
your pop-up is handy for getting an
您的弹出式窗口对于获取
overview and for navigation to the
概述并导航到
individual elements in the file we can
文件中的单个元素，我们可以
also have the same information now is
现在也有相同的信息是
visible in the structure view on the
在结构视图上可见
side the IDE also provides various
IDE还提供了各种功能
inspections and quick fixes for instance
检查和快速修复
we can see that there are some duplicate
我们可以看到有一些重复
parameters in the file we can navigate
我们可以浏览的文件中的参数
over the errors by pressing f2 key after
通过按f2键查看错误后
we navigate it to an error a pop-up will
我们将其导航到一个错误，弹出窗口将
hint us what can we do next to fix the
提示我们下一步该怎么做才能解决
problem the IDE can also detect the
IDE也可以检测到问题
missing configuration parameter in this
在此缺少配置参数
example the verse parameter is missing
示例缺少verse参数
and we can quickly check the
我们可以快速检查
documentation for this parameter to find
查找此参数的文档
out what kind of value is expected as
得出什么样的价值
you can see we have some problems with
你可以看到我们有一些问题
the current file the file requires the
当前文件文件需要
external resources and the ID doesn't
外部资源且ID不
know about those resources yet we can
了解这些资源，但我们可以
add the custom resource definitions in
在以下位置添加自定义资源定义
the settings dialog under the languages
语言下的设置对话框
and frameworks section and they could be
和框架部分，它们可能是
media stab the file is now properly
媒体刺文件现在正确
recognized with no issues and we can
公认没有问题，我们可以
browse the documentation for the
浏览文档以获取
individual elements Elm charts are also
榆木图表的各个元素也
supported let's start by creating a new
支持，让我们从创建一个新的开始
town chart and poet application we can
城镇图和诗人应用程序，我们可以
now use the link tool to validate the
现在使用链接工具来验证
chart the results of printed cheeba
绘制cheeba的结果图表
console and we can navigate to the issue
控制台，我们可以导航到问题
by clicking on the link in this case the
在这种情况下，通过单击链接
icon attribute is missing so we can add
图标属性丢失，因此我们可以添加
it other inspections are provided as
提供其他检查
well for instance the plugin would check
很好，例如插件会检查
the semantic version format in this file
该文件中的语义版本格式
we can also rename the chart safely so
我们还可以安全地重命名图表，以便
not only the name parameter value will
不仅名称参数值会
be changed but also the director
被改变，但导演
that contains the chart definition will
包含图表定义的
be renamed accordingly to preview how
相应地重命名以预览
the individual templates will be
各个模板将是
rendered at the server use the home
在服务器上渲染使用家
template feature the two-sided view
模板功能的双面视图
displays how the placeholders in the
显示占位符在
template are replaced with the actual
模板被替换为实际的
values and within the template we can
值，并且在模板中，我们可以
navigate via the placeholders to the
通过占位符导航到
definition in the values file the code
在值文件中定义代码
folding feature is enabled by default
折叠功能默认启用
and it renders the real values over the
并在
placeholders in the editor we can unfold
我们可以在编辑器中显示占位符
the rendered values to see the actual
呈现的值以查看实际值
placeholder by clicking on the value 4
通过单击值4的占位符
by using a shortcut it's also possible
通过使用快捷方式，这也是可能的
to find all the usages of the individual
查找个人的所有用法
parameters from the values file by using
通过使用值文件中的参数
out at 7 shortcut the requirements that
在7条捷径上提出了以下要求
yama files used to describe the
yama文件用来描述
dependences for the home chart
对本机图表的依赖
right-click on the file select Cooper
右键单击该文件，然后选择Cooper
nearest some dependencies update and
最近的一些依赖项更新和
dependencies will be downloaded into the
依赖项将下载到
chart subdirectory we can even browse
图表子目录，我们甚至可以浏览
the internal files for those charts
这些图表的内部文件
sometimes we each other write the
有时我们彼此写
parameters in the dependencies that is
依赖项中的参数是
the camel file basic completion helps us
骆驼文件的基本完成功能可以帮助我们
to discover the correct parameter to
发现正确的参数
override and the icons in the gutter
覆盖和装订线中的图标
allow us to navigate to the overridden
让我们导航到覆盖
value and back support or customize is
价值和支持或定制是
also included the ID offers completion
还包括ID优惠完成
to the keys and paths and we can rename
到键和路径，我们可以重命名
and navigate to the link resources
并导航到链接资源
in addition find usages action works for
此外，查找用法操作适用于
those files as well I hope you enjoy the
这些文件以及我希望您喜欢
screencast thank you for watching
截屏，谢谢观看
you
您